# 前不久我做了一个吹风机支架
Recently I have made a stand for blowers.
# 这次我准备升级一下它
This time, I am going to upgrade it
# 做一个卫生间的多用机器人
Turn it into a multi-functional restroom robot.
# 给大家介绍一下我做的这个卫生间多功能机器人
Now let me introduce you with the multi-functional robot I've made
# 当你去卫生间方便的时候
When you feel the nature's call
# 您好 欢迎光临
Welcome!
# 当你上完厕所 走的时候
When you finish and walk out
# 谢谢惠顾 请慢走
Have a good one!
# 非常的有礼貌 简简单单一句话
Very polite, which you can tell from the simple words
# 让一个普普通通的卫生间瞬间升级为星级卫生间
It turns a regular loo into a premium washroom
# 大部分卫生间里面的空气也不是特别好
The air quality in most restrooms is not great
# 他头部还有一个净化空气的装置
There is a device to purify the air around it
# 往里面加上香料啊
Add essence oil in here
# 这里还有一个小电扇
Here we have a small fan
# 打开耳朵上的开关
Turn on the switch on its ear
# 它还可以加速香料的挥发
It speeds up the evaporation of essence oil
# 这个空气净化机的下面是一个储物柜
If we look down, there is a storage place
# 打开之后里面可以放一些我们平常的洗漱用品
You can store your toiletries here
# 里面还有一个水龙头和洗手盆
plus a water faucet and a sink
# 平时我们可以在这里洗手
You can wash your hands in here
# 啊 洗头
or wash your hair
# 洗完之后请注意
When you are done washing, check this out
# 关上这个储物柜之后
Close this door
# 这个烘干机就会自动地给我们递到手下面
The blow dryer will automatically move towards you hand
# 把手烘干
and blow dries your hands
# 吹完之后它会自动地复原
It even moves back to its original position once drying is finished
# 拿起之后还可以给你吹下头发之类的
You can also pick it up to blow dry your hair
# 放回去
Put it back
# 自动关闭
It automatically turns off
# 他的另一只手里面还可以放一些卫生纸
On the other hand, you can find toilet paper
# 这样我们方便玩擦屁屁的时候
When we are done and need to wipe
# 只需要对它大喊一声
Just yell at it
# 来纸
PAPER COME!
# 卫生纸就会自动地递到你的面前
It will bring toilet paper to you
# 非常的有仪式感
All done in a ritualistic manner
# 撕完纸之后
Tear off what you need
# 它会自动复原
It reverts to its original position
# 上厕所我比较喜欢玩手机
I like to play my phone on the toilet
# 最害怕手机没有电
And I'm very worried of low battery level
# 所以我在这里安装一个插座
That's why I've installed a power socket in here
# 没电的时候还可以在这里充电
You can charge your phone when it's running low on juice
# 以前我在卫生间里装了一套蹦迪的系统
Previously I have installed a disco system in the restroom
# 但是说一个人蹦有点无聊
But I get a bit bored dancing by myself
# 这个机器人还可以陪你一起蹦迪
This robot can even dance with you
# 现在咱们打开开关试一下
Let's turn on the switch and see